The Basilisk's down!
What's he got equipped?!
This wasn't in the brief!
The fixer fed us false info!
-We're done for…
-Call for back-up!
He's running!
He's headed for Night City.
Don't let Arasaka
take back the cyberskeleton!
So? Where we headed?
Arasaka!
Arasaka… City Center?!
Yeah!
Why Arasaka?!
We're saving Lucy!
Why's she with Arasaka?!
Faraday said she's part
of his deal with them…
I gotta close my eyes a bit…
Again?! Shit, the meds
are wearing off faster…
We've got some Militech company.
Shake them off! David's benched for five.
What?!
-Now?!
-Yeah.
Fine. Five minutes? I'll buy him a nap.
Take the front!
Alrighty, let's get this show on the road!
Way to go, old man!
Nice going!
Shit, another swarm ahead!
Arasaka's up next!
Okie-dokie! Barrel on through!
Not against that number.
We're getting off.
What?! Come on!
Militech's forces are nearly gone.
The target's entered Night City
and our recovery team's on him.
This is going to be hell to cover up…
This is what we get
for putting all our chips on a fixer…
According to path calculations, there's
a 74% chance that he's headed here.
Here? Why?
Can't say. He shouldn't even
know that we're involved.
Damn. Get in contact
with internal security.
Ma'am? The higher ups will be alerted.
Better to stir up a storm
and hide in the dust.
Damn it, Faraday…
Nothing is going according to plan.
Imagine me, a lowly street fixer, meeting
with Arasaka intel inside their own tower.
It's quite the breakthrough,
wouldn't you say?
All who live in this city
should aspire to climb high.
This is but a stepping stone on my way up.
What am I doing…
End of the line!
Wakey, wakey David!
Don't ask where these come from.
Nine times the dosage
of those military-issued meds.
It'll force you to stay sane,
but the side effects'll stack.
By the time ya hit the last vial…
Whatever's left of ya, Davey…
You'll slingshot the other way,
straight over the edge.
Woo-hoo!
Damn. They just keep coming!
Oh shit!
I want you to work hard, rise up,
and get to the top floor of Arasaka Tower!
I know you got it in you, Dee.
Mom!
Thanks, mom. I'll do it.
To the top floor of Arasaka Tower…
Okay.
Let's go. All the way to the top.
I got special meds from Doc.
If I look like I'm losing it,
I need you to shoot me up…
So I can keep it together.
I don't think the meds'll
work on him anymore.
Seriously? What do we do?
We're going to 'Saka!
There's no other option.
But with David like that?
We need Lucy!
What?
She's… the only one
that might be able to bring him back.
I can't think of anyone else that could!
I'm not doing any more jobs for you.
I see…
I understand.
My contract stipulates that I get rid of
anyone who knows about the cyberskeleton.
No exceptions… Not even for you.
Go! After her!
We're getting closer to
the Tower! What's our plan?
When do we ever have a plan?!
David! Do that thing again!
Woo-hoo!
Die! Have some of this!
Persistent bastards!
Cut us a break already!
We lose them?
Most of 'em!
MaxTac!
They sent three AVs?!
They flagged him as a cyberpsycho already?
We're all fucked
if David doesn't get his shit together!
You don't say!
MaxTac was dispatched to dispose of him
as a cyberpsychosis case.
What a nightmare…
This has grown far beyond
our original means.
The boy. We need to stop him
before he makes matters worse.
It's impossible. No one can stop him.
We must wait
for the implant to wear him down.
There is one person who can.
Who?
Adam Smasher.
Y-You're joking.
No, though I'd rather not
have had it come to this.
But even if you summon him now…
That's not a problem.
He's already here.
The cyberskeleton
was originally designed for him.
It's poetic that he should be
the one to end it.
Drop out. Get gone.
Afraid of getting caught?
'Cause I sure ain't.
Fuck you, MaxTac! Come and get us!
What the hell? Hey! Shit!
You're just gonna leave us here?!
Mom!
Is he even human?
Keep shooting!
Hold fire! New orders from Arasaka.
Code A.S. We're retreating.
What?
Rebecca… How many vials are left?
Just one more.
Finally at the end of the rope…
Kiwi?!
Huh?! Two-timing bitch!
I'll fucking kill you!
…Faraday's turn to be betrayed now.
Kiwi has been disposed of.
Nasty business…
Hey!
It can't be… David?!
Don't stop till we reach the loading dock!
Faraday will soon be
arriving with the runner.
As I thought,
Martinez must be after our fixer, not us.
I'll order the AV to turn around.
No, keep them on course for the dock.
You'll meet them there.
I'll meet them?
Someone's going to have to
take the fall for all this mess,
and that person is not me.
Do you understand?
Make sure that mangy fixer
never makes it past the loading dock.
You're up against the cyberskeleton.
Think you might have some fun, Smasher?
It's a child's toy
reliant on antigrav training wheels…
Not even worth my time.
Kill him!
Fire!
Where is he?!
No one's there!
Mom…
Look, I'm at the top of Arasaka Tower.
Well, this is the last one, Doc…
Once you've gone off the edge,
there's no coming back.
Doesn't matter how special you are.
But that's why I gotta go.
'Cause I've got nothing left now.
Seems to me like someone
didn't follow the plan, Faraday.
I brought the girl alive. I believe
our agreed price was one million?
We don't deal with dogs
that run off-leash.
Do you know what happens to
the ones that leave their cages?
Is that a threat? Don't you need
the data inside this cranium?
I can't allow you to take
a single step further in this building.
I would say that's very unwise.
With all the information I have,
it'd be a loss not to keep me on payroll.
Leave the girl and get out.
We'll send the payment as agreed.
We have no further use for you if you
can't give us data on the cyberskeleton…
Lucy…
David…
See that?
I even delivered the cyberskeleton…
You aren't gonna die that easily.
Adam Smasher?!
Kill him!
Who the fuck are you?
You're a merc! Do your fucking job!
My business is with the kid.
Adam Smasher?
So you're Adam Smasher?
Boogeyman of legend?
You're packing some heavy artillery
for your size there, cyberpunk.
Impressive that you're still able to talk.
Likewise, choom.
Heard you went no organic, full cyborg.
You still got a brain in there?
You could say I'm special.
Well so the fuck am I!
That a joke?
Trauma Team!
Thank god…
Can you afford to be distracted?
David! David, can you hear me?
It's me, Lucy!
David, come back to me! Come back…
Lucy…
David…
You installed it.
I knew you would…
And I knew you would die if you did.
I didn't want any of this.
Didn't want you to die…
This is the only way I could
protect you from this city.
I couldn't save mom or Maine,
but I wanted to save you.
But you never had to save me.
All I ever wanted was for you to live.
I don't matter.
I don't have anything left.
You have a dream.
I need you to see it through for me.
That's my dream.
Everything else doesn't matter.
When do you think
those Ara-suckers will give up?
NCPD's out there with them.
It's not gonna be for a while.
Man, I'm almost out of ammo…
We made it.
Took long enough, gonkbrain.
Shut the fuck up!
Falco. Got a favor to ask you.
Alright, time to retreat!
Glad you're back safe.
For David's sake, I mean.
We're having a moment--
Rebecca!
Damn you…
You have a Sandevistan?!
It's a rudimentary implant.
I'm the one you're after!
All the same meat to me.
I'll slaughter each and every one of you.
Not if I kill you first!
Out of meds?
Right on schedule, I'd say.
David!
What?!
Falco… David's still back there…
Falco!
None leave the slaughterhouse alive.
Distracted much?
You…
Who are you… to challenge me…
When you can't even stand
without your antigrav crutches?
Think you're special
'cause you're scrappy?
Don't make me laugh!
Falco! Turn back…
No.
David asked me.
If I go back now…
he'd have died for nothing.
I've got the commission money.
He wants it split between us.
He also told me to tell ya…
Sorry. Wish we could go
to the moon together.
I had fun after all.
You know, you could prove
an interesting construct.
Like I… give a shit…
Alright. Well then.
Welcome to the tour of the moon!
Experience lunar gravity
like nothing you've seen on a BD…
Whoa! Check this!
I can feel the fucking sun!